(Sheldon:)Now...
(Sheldon:)...knowing Penny, the obvious answer is
they engaged in coitus.
But since that's what it looks Iike,
we can rule that out.
Let's put on our thinking caps,
shall we?
Raj is from lndia, a tropical country,
third-world hygiene...
(Sheldon:)...parasitic infections are common,
such as pinworms.
(Sheldon:)- Mm-hm.
- The procedure for diagnosing pinworms...
(Sheldon:)...is to wait until the subject is asleep...
(Sheldon:)...and the worms crawl out of the rectum
for air.
(Sheldon:)Yes, just like that.
(Sheldon:)Penny could have been inspecting
Raj's anal region for parasites.
Oh, boy, that's a true-blue friend.
(Leonard:)They slept together, Sherlock.
No, you weren't Iistening.
She said, "It's not what it looks like."
(Leonard:)She lied.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
Now don't I look silly
sitting here wearing this?